Shikha Umesh Rao

FullStack Developer

Introduction

I am FullStack Developer worked on different technologies based projects like Angular, Nodejs, Java. Also I'm working on Azure related technologies and migrated three applications to Azure. I have 5 years of experience and seeking opportunity to increase my knowledge in these areas and other technologies as well.

Work Expertise

- Angular Developer
 Maintained Angular service
 call with various external
 vendor API for data fetching
 rendering for users.
 -Used css, HTML and javascript
 for developing front end.
- -Used css, HTML and javascript for developing front end.
- -Migrated Twenty plus Microservices jobs in jenkins and configured jobs successfully.
- -Worked with team and migrated 4 application to Azure
- -Working on different Azure technologies like Azure Keyvault ,Virtual Machines , Container registeries, Kubernetes Services , Devops.

Career Summary

Full Stack Developer

Accenture, MIDC Airoli | Aug 2021 - present

- PROJECT HISTORY:

CyberSecurityAppSupport | Aug 2021 - present

In cybersecurity App Support project I'm supporting 5 applications which provides customers to handle theire product details, mitigation reports etc.

Here we handle Customers issues based on Ticketing system. We have Ticket portal where customer connects with operation team and they raise ticket whenever they face any issues related to our application.

We acknowledge those tickets and provide them the required solution. While providing support we also get different enhancement requests in our appliction so we also work on that.

These application are running as docker images on kubernetes cluster. All these applications are build on different technologies like springboot, Angular, Nodejs and its using different DBs like Mysql DB and MongoDB.

While providing the support I have migrated 20 plus microservices jobs on jenkins and build job successfully which required to connect with different teams for resolving the issues , doing ccode changes in jenkins file etc.

While working in this project I have migrated 4 application to Azure. While migrating to Azure I troubleshooted various issues like issues related to microservice deployment on kubernetes cluster, configuring yaml files based on azure support yaml files etc.

Core Skills

Angular6
Angular8
HTML
CSS
JavaScript
Typescript
Basic Github
Node.js
jenkins
Azure Kubernetes
Virtual Machines
Container
resgisteries
Azure Devops
Terraform Scripts

Contact Information

Office: Accenture, MIDC Airoli

Phone: 7208213536

Email:shikharao1997.sr@gmail.com

Education Background

Mumbai University

S.I.E.S College of Arts, Science and Commerce. Sion(West) | APRIL 2018 Graduated with a degree in BSC in Computer Science

MAHARASHTRA BOARD

Mulund VidyaMandir (HSC) | FEBRUARY 2015 Holy Mary Convent High School (SSC) | MARCH 2013

Certification

- -Microsoft Azure Fundamentels AZ 900 -Azure Security Engineer Associate - AZ500 -Git Essentials :Learn Git with Bitbucket and source tree
- -Understanding Typescript 2020 Edition Javascript Certificate

Link - https://github.com/Shikha-rao/certificates.git

After Successful migration I continue to support these applications which incuses renewing certificates, uploading on keyvault and deploying to aks clusters using devops pipeline.

Mainting Kubernetes versions by upgrading to required versions.

Resolving vulnerabilities raised on microservices deployed on Azure Kubernetes cluster by providing relevent code fixes in different technologies like spring boot , nodejs , Angular .

TATA CONSULTANCY SERVICES, Keinsington Powai | sep 2018 - 2021

- PROJECT HISTORY:

Rover Next GEN | Oct'18-May 20

Rover Next GEN is car rental application which provides car to customers to travel from one location to another. It also provides facility to capture the damages of the car by selecting the part of the

images which has been damaged.

We have removed the dependency of an hand held device which was costly and hefty to carry in hand with a simple mobile device with new add on features to enhance the complete business flow.

Redesigned the application into Angular6 ,HTML ,CSS and made it device free(can be used on mobile, tablets and desktops with responsive UI).

Advanced Rebalancer and Goal Planning | Jul 20-Aug 21

Advanced rebalancer and Goal Planning is Citi Bank project.

Advanced rebalancer and Goal Planning is a part of wealth management portal. This project has been migrated from flex code to Angular8. It is desktop based application.

Advanced rebalancer consist of portfolio of the customers transaction.

Goal Planning allowed customer to add goal different goals and also shows different holdings like investment holdings, Liquid Holdings.